(Amy:)Been 15 minutes.
Just sayin'.
(Sheldon:)Okay. I can do this.
(Sheldon:)Just give me a moment...
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Sheldon:)Mimosas coming up.
(Bert:)I once left orange juice
in my fridge so long,
(Bert:)it tasted like a mimosa.
How old was it?
(Bert:)It's hard to say.
(Bert:)I don't remember much
after I drank it.
(Sheldon:)Would you like one,
Mrs. Petrescu?
(Mrs Petrescu:)Yes. Drink is fun
and good friends-- Applebee's.
(Sheldon:)She's learning English from TV.
(Mrs Petrescu:)TV, good. Now back to you.
(Stuart:)Hey, guys.
(Amy:)Hi, Stuart.
(Stuart:)These are for you.
(Amy:)Oh, they're pretty.
Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Stuart, this is Bert
from the Caltech geology lab,
(Sheldon:)and this is Mrs. Petrescu
from downstairs.
(Stuart:)Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Hey.
(Stuart:)So, what did I miss?
(Bert:)Eh, we watched Sheldon
try to open a bottle
(Bert:)for 15 minutes.